

Divyansh Vashisth

Sales Representiative

Motivated and dedicated sales executive with 1+ years of experience in boosting sales and costumer loyalty through individualized and group service. Resourceful expert at learning costumer needs, directing to desirable merchandise and upselling to meet the sales quotas committed to strengthening costumer experiences with positivity and professionalism when answering requests and processing



divyanshvashisth@gmail.com



7526950432



Zirakpur, India



WORK EXPERIENCE

Sports Leader Decathlon Sports

10/2022 - 06/2023

Zirakpur, India

Role as a sport leader

- Stock Management Establish a clear process for returns and damages, ensuring accurate deliveries to customers.
- Inventory Management Ensuring enough goods to meet with costumer demands.
- Sales Analysis Performance in business in terms of sales.
- Local Sports Project Engaging in sports developing projects within the localities.
- Community Building Building connections and interact with them.
- Conduct Newcomers Training to newcomers about all the management.
- Costumer Interaction Guide customer interactions to enhance feedback.

Sales representiative

Teleperformance

07/2023 - Present

Mohali, India

Role as a online sale specialist

- Excellent Communication Skills Proficient in written communication with a keen focus on clarity and empathy.
- Multitasking and Time Management Juggle multiple chats with precision, ensuring top-notch quality and attention to detail.
- Product Knowledge In-depth understanding of the company's products/services to provide accurate and relevant information to customers.
- Problem-Solving Skills Proactively identify and resolve potential problems to enhance overall customer satisfaction.
- Adaptability Ability to adapt to new technologies and tools quickly.
- Team Collaboration Collaborate with colleagues to share insights and improve overall customer experience.
- Continuous Improvement Focus Actively seek feedback and participate in training programs.



EDUCATION

B.C.A - Bachelor in Computer Applications Sri Guru Gobind Singh College

2021 - Present

2019 - 2021

Senior Secondary

Dev Samaj Sr. Sec School

Secondary Stepping Stones Sr. Sec School 7.0 CGPA



SKILLS

Leadership

Communication skills

Web Development

Team Work

Adaptability



PERSONAL PROJECTS

Communication (Sinage Project)

 Designed communication for fitness equipment in Decathlon.

Event management

 Organized events for Decathlon to cover every audience.



ACHIEVEMENTS

N.C.C Certificate (2019 - 2021)

National Cadet Corps - Junior Commander

Rao Jai Singh Basketball Tournament (2021)

Certificate of Participation

Inter-School Yoga Competition

2nd prize in Chandigarh Under-12 Yoga Category



LANGUAGES

English

Full Professional Proficiency

Full Professional Proficiency

Punjabi

Full Professional Proficiency



Sports

Fitness

Travel

2017 - 2019 6.8 CCPA